decalgirl.com 2014-07-01

# Privacy Policy | DecalGirl

###  Protecting your privacy is important to DecalGirl. We strive to keep your personal information confidential. By ensuring that you are aware of and understand the DecalGirl Customer Privacy Policy, we can provide you with better service. Please take a moment to read the following policy to learn how we handle your personal information. 

### Why We Collect Personal Information

DecalGirl collects and uses your personal information to give you superior customer service, to provide you with convenient access to our products and services, and to make a wider range available to you. In addition, we use your personal information to keep you up to date on the latest service, special offers, and other information we think you'd like to hear about. 

From time to time, we may also use your personal information to contact you in regards to keeping you updated of new DecalGirl products, artists, designs and special offers. If you no longer wish to receive these types of email communications you may opt-out at anytime. Please see the choice/opt-out section below. 

If you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). 

We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you. 

### How We Collect Personal Information

We collect information about you in several ways. For example, we might ask for your contact information when you correspond with us, call us to make a purchase or request service, or participate in an online survey. In addition, when you complete your online order, we collect and store the information you provide in a secure database. 

To save you time and make our web services even easier to use, some areas of the DecalGirl website allow you to create a "DecalGirl User Account" using your personal information. Here's how it works: Simply fill out a brief profile: your name and email address; then choose a password for security. The system saves your information and assigns you a personal DecalGirl User Account. Next time you order something from DecalGirl, you can simply enter your email address and password and the system will automatically look up the information it needs. 

### When We Disclose Personal Information

#### Agents/Service Providers

We use other third parties such as a shipping company to fulfill orders, and a credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services, an email service provider to send out emails on our behalf and a third party marketing provider to provide broadcast email services for us. We use Live Chat to assist you if you have questions while using our site or regarding your order. When you sign up for MyBuy Alerts, we will share your email address and opt-in status as necessary for the third party to provide that service. 

These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for promotional purposes. We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site. 

DecalGirl does not share, sell, rent, or trade PII with third parties other than as stated within this privacy policy. 

### Choice/Opt-out

We provide you the opportunity to "opt-out" of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when we ask for this information. For example, if you purchase a product/service but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate your preference on our order form. 

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us at [privacy@decalgirl](mailto:privacy@decalgirl.com).com. We offer an opportunity to opt-out of certain communications on our Email Updates page as well as our "My Account" section, or you may contact us at [support@decalgirl.com](mailto:support@decalgirl.com) or by mail to DecalGirl, Attn: Privacy, 25448 Prime Hook Rd, Suite 400, Milton, DE 19968, USA to opt-out. 

### We protect your personal information

DecalGirl safeguards the security of the data you send us with physical, electronic, and managerial procedures. We urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Change your passwords often, use a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure you use a secure browser. 

DecalGirl uses industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption on all web pages where personal information is required. To place on-line orders with DecalGirl, you must use an SSL-enabled browser such as Netscape Navigator 3.0 or later, or Internet Explorer. This protects the confidentiality of your personal and credit card information while it is transmitted over the Internet. 

### Data Retention

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. Please contact us if you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

### Cookies

When you browse DecalGirl's website, you are able to do so anonymously. Generally, we don't collect personal information when you browse - not even your email address. Your browser, however, does automatically tell us the type of computer and operating system you are using. 

Like many websites, the DecalGirl website uses cookie technology. When you first connect to our site, the cookie identifies your browser with a unique, random number. The cookies we use are not linked to any personal information about you. Cookies help us understand which parts of our websites are the most popular, where our visitors are going, and how long they spend there. We use cookies to study traffic patterns on our site so we can make the site even better. 

### Third Party Cookies

The use of cookies by third parties is not covered by our privacy policy. We do not have access or control over these cookies. These third parties use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site, in order for you to use the shopping cart. 

### Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)

We employ [or our third party advertising partner employs] a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We tie [do not tie] the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personally identifiable information. 

### Social Media Features and Widgets

Our web site includes social media features, such as the Facebook Like button and widgets, such as the ShareThis button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our web site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 

### Tell-A-Friend

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend (send to a friend) about our site, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. DecalGirl does not store this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email (and tracking the success of our referral program). Your friend may contact us at [support@decalgirl.com](mailto:support@decalgirl.com) to request that we remove this information from our database. 

### Blog/Forum

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at [support@decalgirl.com](mailto:support@decalgirl.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why. 

###  Updating, Deleting or Correcting Personally Identifiable Information 

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, delete or update it by making the change on our member information page or by emailing our Customer Support at support@decalgirl.com or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below. 

### Our Companywide Commitment to Privacy

To make sure your personal information remains confidential, we communicate these privacy guidelines to every DecalGirl employee. DecalGirl does not knowingly solicit personal information from children or send them requests for personal information. 

This website contains links to other sites. DecalGirl does not share your personal information with those websites and is not responsible for their privacy practices. We encourage you to learn about the privacy policies of those companies. 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy policy, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. 

This policy is effective February 5, 2014.
